Guide to the Firebrand Books records, 1984-2000.
Firebrand Books records,
- Series I. Author/Book Files
  - A Gathering of Spirit: Pending, 1989-1995 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: Contracts, 1988-2000 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: by Beth Brant, ed., Sinister Wisdom Books 1984 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: (Canadian Edition) by Beth Brant, ed., The Women's Press 1984, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: General, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: General, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: General, 1996-1997 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: General, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: General, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: General, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: General, 1990-1991 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: General, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: A Collection by North American Indian Women by Beth Brant, ed., Firebrand Books 1984, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: Reviews, 1989-2000 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - A Gathering of Spirit: Review Copies, 1989-2000 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Getting Home Alive: Pending, 1986-1996 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Getting Home Alive: Contracts, 1985-2000 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Getting Home Alive: General, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Getting Home Alive: General, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Getting Home Alive: General, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Getting Home Alive: General, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Getting Home Alive: General, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Getting Home Alive: General, 1994-1995 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Getting Home Alive: General, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Getting Home Alive: General, 1991-1992 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Getting Home Alive: General, 1988-1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Getting Home Alive: General, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Getting Home Alive: General, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Getting Home Alive: General, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Getting Home Alive: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Getting Home Alive: by Aurora Levins Morales and Rosario Morales, Firebrand Books 1986 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Getting Home Alive: Reviews, 1986-1992 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Getting Home Alive: Review Copies, 1986-1999 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - The Gilda Stories: Pending, 1991-1999 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - The Gilda Stories: Contracts, 1989-2000 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - The Gilda Stories: (British Edition) by Jewelle Gomez, Sheba Feminist Publishers 1991, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - The Gilda Stories: General, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - The Gilda Stories: General, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - The Gilda Stories: General, 1993-1995 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - The Gilda Stories: General, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - The Gilda Stories: General, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - The Gilda Stories: General, 1986-1990 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - The Gilda Stories: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - The Gilda Stories: A Novel by Jewelle Gomez, Firebrand Books 1991 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - The Gilda Stories: Reviews, 1991-2000 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - The Gilda Stories: Review Copies, 1991-2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Good Enough to Eat: Pending, 1986-1994 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Good Enough to Eat: Contracts, 1985-2000 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Good Enough to Eat: (British Edition) by Lesléa Newman, Sheba Feminist Publishers 1986, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Good Enough to Eat: General, 1992-2000 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Good Enough to Eat: General, 1987-1991 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Good Enough to Eat: General, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Good Enough to Eat: General, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Good Enough to Eat: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Good Enough to Eat: A Novel by Lesléa Newman, Firebrand Books 1986 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Good Enough to Eat: Reviews, 1986-1997 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Good Enough to Eat: Review Copies, 1986-2000 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Horseshoe Sky: Pending, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Horseshoe Sky: Contracts, 1994-2000 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Horseshoe Sky: General, 1994-2000 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Horseshoe Sky: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Horseshoe Sky: A Novel by Catherine Koger, Firebrand Books 1995 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Horseshoe Sky: Reviews, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Horseshoe Sky: Review Copies, 1995-1997 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Hot, Throbbing Dykes to Watch Out For: Pending, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Hot, Throbbing Dykes to Watch Out For: Contracts, 1996-2000 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Turbogeile Lesbenlust: (Hot, Throbbing Dykes to Watch Out For-German Edition) by Alison Bechdel, Daphne 1997, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Hot, Throbbing Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Hot, Throbbing Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Hot, Throbbing Dykes to Watch Out For: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Hot, Throbbing Dykes to Watch Out For: Cartoons by Alison Bechdel, Firebrand Books 1997 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Hot, Throbbing Dykes to Watch Out For: Reviews, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Hot, Throbbing Dykes to Watch Out For: Review Copies, 1997-1999 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Humid Pitch: Pending, 1989 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Humid Pitch: Contracts, 1987-2000 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Humid Pitch: General, 1991-2000 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Humid Pitch: General, 1987-1990 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Humid Pitch: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Humid Pitch: Narrative Poetry by Cheryl Clarke, Firebrand Books 1989 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Humid Pitch: Reviews, 1989-1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Humid Pitch: Review Copies, 1989-1999 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - The Indelible Alison Bechdel: Pending, 1997-1999 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - The Indelible Alison Bechdel: Contracts, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - The Indelible Alison Bechdel: General, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - The Indelible Alison Bechdel: General, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - The Indelible Alison Bechdel: General, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - The Indelible Alison Bechdel: Promo Materials (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - The Indelible Alison Bechdel: by Alison Bechdel, Firebrand Books 1998 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - The Indelible Alison Bechdel: Reviews, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - The Indelible Alison Bechdel: Review Copies, 1998-2000 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Jewish Women's Call For Peace: Contracts, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Jewish Women's Call For Peace: General, 1990-1996 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Jewish Women's Call For Peace: General, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Jewish Women's Call For Peace: A Handbook for Jewish Women on the Israeli/Palestinian Conflict, Firebrand Books 1990 and Promo materials (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Jewish Women's Call For Peace: Reviews, 1990-1991 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Jewish Women's Call For Peace: Review Copies, 1990-1996 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Jonestown & Other Madness: Pending, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Jonestown & Other Madness: Contracts, 1984-2000 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Jonestown & Other Madness: General, 1994-2000 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Jonestown & Other Madness: General, 1989-1993 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Jonestown & Other Madness: General, 1986-1988 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Jonestown & Other Madness: General, 1984-1985 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Jonestown & Other Madness: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Jonestown & Other Madness: Poetry by Pat Parker, Firebrand Books 1985 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Jonestown & Other Madness: Reviews, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Jonestown & Other Madness: Review Copies, 1985-2000 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Just Say Yes: Pending, 1990-1996 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Just Say Yes: Contracts, 1990-2000 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Just Say Yes: General, 1991-2000 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Just Say Yes: General, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Just Say Yes: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Just Say Yes: A Novel by Judith McDaniel, Firebrand Books 1991 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Just Say Yes: Reviews, 1991-1999 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Just Say Yes: Review Copies, 1990-1999 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - The Land of Look Behind: Pending, 1985-1991 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - The Land of Look Behind: Contracts, 1984-1999 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - The Land of Look Behind: General, 1997-2000 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - The Land of Look Behind: General, 1995-1996 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - The Land of Look Behind: General, 1993-1994 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - The Land of Look Behind: General, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - The Land of Look Behind: General, 1987-1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - The Land of Look Behind: General, 1984-1986 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - The Land of Look Behind: Promo Materials (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - The Land of Look Behind: by Michelle Cliff, Firebrand Books 1985 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - The Land of Look Behind: Reviews, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - The Land of Look Behind: Review Copies, 1985-1999 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Legal Tender: Pending, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Legal Tender: Contracts, 1991-2000 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Legal Tender: Contracts (German), 1990-2000 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Legal Tender: (British Edition) A Mystery by Marion Foster, The Women's Press Ltd. 1992, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Wen die Macht ihr Netz auswirft: (Legal Tender-German Edition) by Marion Foster, Argument Verlag 1992 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Legal Tender: General, 1988-2000 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Legal Tender: Promo Materials (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Legal Tender: A Mystery by Marion Foster, Firebrand Books 1992 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Legal Tender: Reviews, 1992-1995 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Legal Tender: Review Copies, 1992-2000 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Lesbian (Out)Law: Pending, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Lesbian (Out)Law: Contracts, 1990-2000 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Lesbian (Out)Law: General, 1998-2000 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Lesbian (Out)Law: General, 1993-1997 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Lesbian (Out)Law: General, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Lesbian (Out)Law: General, 1989-1991 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Lesbian (Out)Law: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Lesbian (Out)Law: Survival Under the Rule of Law by Ruthann Robson, Firebrand Books 1992 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Lesbian (Out)Law: Reviews, 1992-1998 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Lesbian (Out)Law: Review Copies, 1992-2000 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - A Letter to Harvey Milk: Pending, 1987-1994 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - A Letter to Harvey Milk: Contracts, 1987-2000 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - A Letter to Harvey Milk: video cassette "Harry Weinberg's Notebook," directed by Yariv Kohn, n.d.; V-9863 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - A Letter to Harvey Milk: General, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - A Letter to Harvey Milk: General, 1996-1998 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - A Letter to Harvey Milk: General, 1994-1995 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - A Letter to Harvey Milk: General, 1991-1993 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - A Letter to Harvey Milk: General, 1988-1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - A Letter to Harvey Milk: General, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - A Letter to Harvey Milk: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - A Letter to Harvey Milk: Short Stories by Lesléa Newman, Firebrand Books 1988 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - A Letter to Harvey Milk: Reviews, 1988-1998 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - A Letter to Harvey Milk: Review Copies, 1988-1998 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Letting in the Night: Pending, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Letting in the Night: Contracts, 1988-2000 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Letting in the Night: General, 1988-2000 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Letting in the Night: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Letting in the Night: A Novel by Joan Lindau, Firebrand Books 1989 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Letting in the Night: Reviews, 1989-1995 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Letting in the Night: Review Copies, 1989-1996 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Living as a Lesbian: Pending, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Living as a Lesbian: Contracts, 1984-2000 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Living as a Lesbian: General, 1997-2000 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Living as a Lesbian: General, 1993-1996 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Living as a Lesbian: General, 1988-1992 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Living as a Lesbian: General, 1986-1987 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Living as a Lesbian: General, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Living as a Lesbian: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Living as a Lesbian: Poetry by Cheryl Clarke, Firebrand Books 1986 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Living as a Lesbian: Reviews, 1986-1992 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Living as a Lesbian: Review Copies, 1986-1999 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Love and Death, and Other Disasters: Pending, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Love and Death, and Other Disasters: Contracts, 1996-2000 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Love and Death, and Other Disasters: General, 1998-2000 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Love and Death, and Other Disasters: General, 1988-1997 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Love and Death, and Other Disasters: Promo Materials (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Love and Death, and Other Disasters: Stories 1977-1995 by Jenifer Levin, Firebrand Books 1996 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Love and Death, and Other Disasters: Reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Love and Death, and Other Disasters: Review Copies, 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Making It: Contracts, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Making It: General, 1992-1998 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Making It: General, 1990-1991 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Making It: General, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Making It: General, 1988 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Making It: General, 1987 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Making It: General, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Making It: A Woman's Guide to Sex in the Age of Aids by Cindy Patton and Janice Kelly, Firebrand Books 1987 and promo materials (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Making It: Reviews, 1987-1993 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Making It: Review Copies, 1991-1993 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Making It: Review Copies, 1987-1990 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Metamorphosis: Pending, 1988-1989 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Metamorphosis: Contracts, 1989-2000 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Metamorphosis: General, 1990-2000 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Metamorphosis: General, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Metamorphosis: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Metamorphosis: Reflections of Recovery by Judith McDaniel, Firebrand Books 1989 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Metamorphosis: Reviews, 1989-1990 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Metamorphosis: Review Copies, 1989-1999 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Mohawk Trail: Pending, 1989-2000 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Mohawk Trail: Contracts, 1984-2000 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Mohawk Trail: General, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Mohawk Trail: General, 1994-1998 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Mohawk Trail: General, 1990-1993 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Mohawk Trail: General, 1986-1989 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Mohawk Trail: General, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Mohawk Trail: General, 1982-1983 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Mohawk Trail: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Mohawk Trail: (Canadian Edition) by Beth Brant, Women's Press 1985 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Mohawk Trail: Reviews, 1985-1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Mohawk Trail: Review Copies, 1985-1998 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Moll Cutpurse: Pending, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Moll Cutpurse: Contracts, 1987-2000 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Moll Cutpurse: General, 1984-2000 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Moll Cutpurse: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Moll Cutpurse: A Novel by Allen Galford, Firebrand Books 1985 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Moll Cutpurse: Reviews, 1984-1997 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Moll Cutpurse: Review Copies, 1985-1997 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - The Monarchs Are Flying: Pending, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - The Monarchs Are Flying: Contracts, 1986-2000 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - The Monarchs Are Flying: Contracts (British and Canadian rights), 1987-2000 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - The Monarchs Are Flying: Contracts (German rights), 1988-2000 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - The Monarchs Are Flying: by Marion Foster, Pandora Press 1987, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Wenn die grauen Falter fliegen: (The Monarchs Are Flying-German Edition) by Marion Foster, Argument Verlag 1988 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - The Monarchs Are Flying: General, 198-2000 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - The Monarchs Are Flying: General, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - The Monarchs Are Flying: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - The Monarchs Are Flying: A Novel by Marion Foster, Firebrand Books 1987 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - The Monarchs Are Flying: Reviews, 1987-1992 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - The Monarchs Are Flying: Review Copies, 1987-2000 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - More Dykes to Watch Out For: Pending, 1987-1998 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - More Dykes to Watch Out For: Contracts, 1986-2000 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Lesbenlënlaufe...wie aus dem Bilderbuch: (More Dykes to Watch Out For-German Edition) by Alison Bechdel, Daphne 1988, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - More Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1998-2000 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - More Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1991-1997 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - More Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1987-1990 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - More Dykes to Watch Out For: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - More Dykes to Watch Out For: Cartoons by Alison Bechdel, Firebrand Books 1988 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - More Dykes to Watch Out For: Reviews, 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - More Dykes to Watch Out For: Review Copies, 1988-1999 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Movement in Black: Pending, 1989-1999 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Movement in Black: Contracts, 1989-2000 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Movement in Black: Poetry by Pat Parker, Firebrand Books 1978, 1983, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Movement in Black: General, 2000-2001 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Movement in Black: General, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Movement in Black: General, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Movement in Black: General, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Movement in Black: General, 1996-1997 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Movement in Black: General, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Movement in Black: General, 1992-1993 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Movement in Black: General, 1989-1991 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Movement in Black: General, 1974-1988 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Movement in Black: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Expanded Edition of Movement in Black: Poetry by Pat Parker, Firebrand Books 1999 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Movement in Black: Reviews, 1990-2000 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Movement in Black: Review Copies, 1989-1999 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - My Mama's Dead Squirrel: Pending, 1985-1991 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - My Mama's Dead Squirrel: Contracts, 1984-2000 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - My Mama's Dead Squirrel: General, 1998-2000 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - My Mama's Dead Squirrel: General, 1991-1997 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - My Mama's Dead Squirrel: General, 1987-1990 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - My Mama's Dead Squirrel: General, 1985-1986 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - My Mama's Dead Squirrel: General, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - My Mama's Dead Squirrel: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - My Mama's Dead Squirrel: Lesbian Essays on Southern Culture by Mab Segrest, Firebrand Books 1985 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - My Mama's Dead Squirrel: Reviews, 1985-1997 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - My Mama's Dead Squirrel: Review Copies, 1985-1999 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Natural Birth: Pending, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Natural Birth: Contracts, 1999-2000 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Natural Birth: General, 1998-2000 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Natural Birth: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Natural Birth: by Toi Derricotte, Firebrand Books 2000 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Natural Birth: Reviews, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Natural Birth: Review Copies, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - New, Improved! Dykes to Watch Out For: Pending, 1990-1997 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - New, Improved! Dykes to Watch Out For: Contracts, 1988-2000 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Die feine Lesbenart: (New, Improved! Dykes to Watch Out For-German Edition) by Alison Bechdel, Daphne 1990, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - New, Improved! Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1997-2000 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - New, Improved! Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1992-1996 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - New, Improved! Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1990-1991 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - New, Improved! Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1988-1989 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - New, Improved! Dykes to Watch Out For: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - New, Improved! Dykes to Watch Out For: Cartoons by Alison Bechdel, Firebrand Books 1990 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - New, Improved! Dykes to Watch Out For: Reviews, 1990-1992 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - New, Improved! Dykes to Watch Out For: Review Copies, 1990-1999 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Normal Sex: Pending, 1993-1994 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Normal Sex: Contracts, 1993-2000 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Normal Sex: General, 1996-2000 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Normal Sex: General, 1993-1995 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Normal Sex: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Normal Sex: Poetry by Linda Smukler, Firebrand Books 1994 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Normal Sex: Reviews, 1994-1995 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Normal Sex: Review Copies, 1994-1998 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Now Poof She Is Gone: Pending, 1994 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Now Poof She Is Gone: Contracts, 1993-2000 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Now Poof She Is Gone: General, 1992-2000 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Now Poof She Is Gone: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Now Poof She Is Gone: Poetry by Wendy Rose, Firebrand Books 1994 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Now Poof She Is Gone: Reviews, 1994-1998 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Now Poof She Is Gone: Review Copies, 1994-1997 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Oral Tradition: Pending, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Oral Tradition: Contracts, 1995-2000 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Oral Tradition: cassette tape-Out Write '98 Audre Lorde Lecture, 1998; tr-11673 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Oral Tradition: General, 1997-2000 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Oral Tradition: General, 1994-1996 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Oral Tradition: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Oral Tradition: Selected Poems Old & New by Jewelle Gomez, Firebrand Books 1995 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Oral Tradition: Reviews, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Oral Tradition: Review Copies, 1995-1998 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - The Other Sappho: Pending, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - The Other Sappho: Contracts, 1988-2000 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - The Other Sappho: General, 1991-2000 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - The Other Sappho: General, 1988-1990 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - The Other Sappho: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - The Other Sappho: A Novel by Ellen Frye, Firebrand Books 1989 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - The Other Sappho: Reviews, 1989-1995 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - The Other Sappho: Review Copies, 1989-2000 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Out in the World: Contracts, 1991 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Out in the World: General, 1990-1998 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Out in the World: International Lesbian Organizing by Shelley Anderson, Firebrand Books 1991 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Out in the World: Reviews, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Out in the World: Review Copies, 1991-1996 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Parker & Hulme: Pending, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Parker & Hulme: Contracts, 1995-2000 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Parker & Hulme: A Lesbian View (New Zealand Edition) by Julie Glamuzina & Alison J. Laurie, New Women's Press 1991 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Parker & Hulme: General 1991-2000 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Out Front: Lesbian Political Ativity in Aotearoa 1962-1985 by Julie Glamuzina, Lesbian Press 1993 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Parker & Hulme: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Parker & Hulme: A Lesbian View by Julie Glamuzina & Alison J. Laurie, Firebrand Books 1991, 1995 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Parker & Hulme: Reviews, 1996-1998 (Box 18, Folder 17)